Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/zachkirkrey (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js

Angular

Vue.js

Languages

Portuguese (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Limited Working)

Zachary Reynolds

Senior Full Stack Developer (React, Angular, Vue, NodeJS, Laravel, Python, C#)

Knoxville, Tennessee, United States

Summary

As a passionate and professional Senior Full Stack Developer with over 8 years of experience in website and hybrid/native mobile app development, I have extensive knowledge of modern JS libraries such as React, Angular, and Vue for front-end and Node.js, C#, .NET, Python, PHP, Laravel, MySQL, MongoDB and PostgreSQL for the back end. Am especially familiar with web hosting using AWS Services, Firebase, Heroku, and GCP. I'm also a self-motivated, and creative developer in hybrid mobile app development with React Native and as I've worked for both small and large companies, I've been working in a startup and fortune 500 companies for several years and always provided top-notch products.

Main Skills:

- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4/5, SCSS, Sass/Less, Tailwind CSS
- JavaScript, Typescript,
- React Native, React.js, Redux.js, JSX, Gatsby.js, Next.js
- Angular 6+, Angular CLI, Ngrx, RxJS
- Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify, Nuxt.js
- Material UI, Chakra UI, Ant Design
- Node.js, Express.js
- C#, .NET, ASP.NET
- Python, Django, Flask
- PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, Yii
- MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Redis, MariaDB
- AWS Services, Netlify, Vercel, Firebase, Heroku, GCP
- CI/CD pipelines, Jenkins
- Docker, Kubernetes
- Unit Testing, Jest, Mocha, Chai
- Git, GitHub, GitLab, BitBucket
- Jira, Trello, Asana, ClickUp

The service industry increased my leadership skills and knowledge to grow customer relations and retention. In addition, triggering my desire to contribute quality code as a developer with user experience at the forefront enhanced by visual design and logistical programs to improve business solutions.

I would like to opportunity to show my talents and ability to companies or clients that value hard-working software engineers eager to hit the ground running and make an instant impact.

Experience

Theseus AI Senior Full Stack Software Developer November 2019 - April 2022 (2 years 6 months) Knoxville, Tennessee, United States

- -Full stack software engineer with a focus on Angular/Python programming/ architecture and the AWS ecosystem of services; including Lambda, API Gateway, Amplify, Cognito, Athena, S3, and others as needed.
- Facilitate the creation of a robust suite of cloud-native applications in the rapidly growing healthcare software industry.
- -Collaborate with others on an agile development team to deliver DSCSA compliant software that sustains and improves the health of individuals and communities.
- -Contributor in the overall system architecture and ongoing development of applications.

MailTag

Senior Full Stack Lead Developer December 2018 - October 2019 (11 months)

Knoxville, Tennessee, United States

- Designed and developed an Email Tool Chrome extension from scratch.
- Worked on both Front-end (React.js, Styled Components, Material UI) and Back-end (Node.js, Adonis.js) and deployed to AWS
- Iterated testing the functionalities, bugfixing, and maintenance
- Successfully launched the app and get certification from Google.

rEvolution
Senior Full Stack Engineer
February 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Knoxville, Tennessee, United States

- Full-Stack development of web and native mobile applications for clients in a wide variety of industries
- API design and development
- Technologies and langauges used on a day-to-day basis include React, React Native, Nodejs, MySQL, Postgres, MongoDB, Docker, and Stripe integration.
- Built and maintained fully custom-coded WordPress websites

pozible

Senior Software Developer

March 2015 - December 2016 (1 year 10 months)

Knoxville, Tennessee, United States

- Wrote PHP, MySQL, and JavaScript / jQuery code for a web application that tracks project management data for client vendors.
- Developed a feature that allows our vendors to dynamically generate quotes and invoices through our application, sign them, and send them via email as fully functional PDF contracts.
- Responsible for implementing Version Control (Git) for our team, leading to an improved test-to-production workflow model

Education

University of Tennessee, Knoxville

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (2010 - 2014)

University of Utah College of Engineering
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Mathematics and Computer
Science · (2008 - 2010)